http://www.rugbystore.co.uk/help/privacy-policy

XMAS INFOCovid-19 InfoHelpSize ChartDeliveryReturnsGift Vouchers
UK Freephone: 0800 298 4352
Create Account
Login
CHRISTMASCHRISTMAS STORE HOMEGifts to PersonaliseFor HimFor HerFor KidsStocking FillersLIONSBRITISH & IRISH LIONSView All British & Irish LionsMensWomensKidsAccessoriesINTERNATIONAL TEAMS6 NATIONSEnglandScotlandIrelandWalesFranceItaly6 Nations CollectionView AllRUGBY CHAMPIONSHIPSNew Zealand All BlacksAustralia WallabiesSouth Africa SpringboksArgentinaView AllOTHER INTERNATIONAL TEAMSBarbariansBritish & Irish LionsInternational Rugby LeagueOther TeamsView AllRUGBY WORLD CUPOfficial Licensed Clothing & AccessoriesRugby World Cup BallsCLUB TEAMSGallagher PremiershipBathLeicester TigersNewcastle FalconsNorthampton SaintsSaracensGuinness Pro14Edinburgh RugbyGlasgow WarriorsOspreysScarletsUlster RugbyEuropean Rugby Champions CupBath RugbyEdinburgh RugbyGlasgow WarriorsLeicester TigersSaracensScarletsUlster RugbySuper RugbyBluesChiefsCrusadersHighlandersHurricanesFrench Top 14ASM ClermontCastresLa RochelleMontpellierToulonToulouseForces RugbyArmyView...View All Rugby shirtsTRAINING & OFF FIELDMENS TRAINING & OFF FIELDRugby ShirtsTee ShirtsPolo ShirtsHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & FleecesBottoms & TrousersShortsSocksBase LayerUnderwearHats, Caps, Gloves & ScarvesRunning ShoesFlip Flops & SlidesKIDS TRAINING & OFF FIELDRugby ShirtsTee ShirtsPolo ShirtsHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & FleecesBottoms & TrousersShortsSocksKids Base LayerHats, Caps, Gloves & ScarvesWOMENS TRAINING & OFF FIELDBase LayerHats, Gloves & ScarvesHoodies, Jackets & SweatsRunning Shoes & SlidesShorts & BottomsSports Bras, Underwear & SocksTeam ReplicaTee Shirts & VestsRUGBY BOOTSBOOTS BY BRANDAll Rugby BootsadidasAsicsCanterburyGilbertMizunoNikeOptimumVIEW...Adults Rugby BootsKids Rugby BootsAll Sale Rugby BootsRS Top 10 BootsSOLE TYPE & POSITIONFirm Ground BootsSoft Ground BootsBacks BootsForwards bootsBOOT ACCESSORIESFootwear ExtrasInsolesWOMENS RUGBYTeam ReplicaView AllEngland InternationalScotland InternationalWales InternationalRugby BootsView AllBacks BootsForwards bootsBody ProtectionView AllHeadguardsShoulder PadsMouthguardsSports Bras, Underwear, SocksView AllSports BrasCompression SocksPlaying & Training SocksBase LayerView AllTop HalfBottom HalfHoodies, Jackets, TopsView AllHoodiesJacketsTopsT-Shirts, Vests, Tanks View AllT-ShirtsVests, TanksCompression TeesHats, Gloves, ScarvesView AllShorts & BottomsView AllShortsBaselayerBottoms & TrousersRunning shoes, SlidesView AllGym EquipmentView AllPROTECTION & EQUIPMENTPROTECTIVE WEARHeadguardsShoulder padsMouthguardsRUGBY BALLSMatch BallsTraining BallsTeam & Other BallsRugby World Cup BallsPumps & AdaptorsTRAINING EQUIPMENTGym & Home FitnessTackle Bags & TubesRucking ShieldsAgility TrainingBall Carry BagsTraining BibsRugby PostsPitch AccessoriesPLAYER ACCESSORIESDrinks BottlesKicking TeesHoldalls, Bags, BackpacksMittsGrip Sprays, WaxTrionZ Magnetic TherapyINJURY MANAGEMENTSupportsTaping, StrappingHot & Cold TherapyFirst Aid KidsRUGBY TEAMWEARADIDASShirtsShortsSocksCANTERBURYMensWomensKidsGILBERTMensWomensKidsUNBRANDED TEAMWEARMensWomensKidsGirlsWACKYSOXAdultsKidsBRANDSAdidasCanterburyGilbertMacronOptimumUmbroUnder ArmourSALEMENBootsTeam ReplicaTraining & Off-FieldProtection & EquipmentWOMENBootsTeam ReplicaTraining & Off-FieldProtection & EquipmentKIDSBootsTeam ReplicaTraining & Off-FieldProtection & EquipmentCOLLECTIONSView All Sale ProductsRugby World Cup 2019BootsProtection & EquipmentNew Zealand All BlacksEnglandScotland
Search
17169 reviews
CREATE ACCOUNT | LOGIN
Basket - 0 item(s) £0.00
Your basket is empty.
CHRISTMASCHRISTMAS STORE HOMEGifts to PersonaliseFor HimFor HerFor KidsStocking FillersLIONSBRITISH & IRISH LIONSView All British & Irish LionsMensWomensKidsAccessoriesINTERNATIONAL TEAMS6 NATIONSEnglandScotlandIrelandWalesFranceItaly6 Nations CollectionView AllRUGBY CHAMPIONSHIPSNew Zealand All BlacksAustralia WallabiesSouth Africa SpringboksArgentinaView AllOTHER INTERNATIONAL TEAMSBarbariansBritish & Irish LionsInternational Rugby LeagueOther TeamsView AllRUGBY WORLD CUPOfficial Licensed Clothing & AccessoriesRugby World Cup BallsCLUB TEAMSGallagher PremiershipBathLeicester TigersNewcastle FalconsNorthampton SaintsSaracensGuinness Pro14Edinburgh RugbyGlasgow WarriorsOspreysScarletsUlster RugbyEuropean Rugby Champions CupBath RugbyEdinburgh RugbyGlasgow WarriorsLeicester TigersSaracensScarletsUlster RugbySuper RugbyBluesChiefsCrusadersHighlandersHurricanesFrench Top 14ASM ClermontCastresLa RochelleMontpellierToulonToulouseForces RugbyArmyView...View All Rugby shirtsTRAINING & OFF FIELDMENS TRAINING & OFF FIELDRugby ShirtsTee ShirtsPolo ShirtsHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & FleecesBottoms & TrousersShortsSocksBase LayerUnderwearHats, Caps, Gloves & ScarvesRunning ShoesFlip Flops & SlidesKIDS TRAINING & OFF FIELDRugby ShirtsTee ShirtsPolo ShirtsHoodies & SweatshirtsJackets & FleecesBottoms & TrousersShortsSocksKids Base LayerHats, Caps, Gloves & ScarvesWOMENS TRAINING & OFF FIELDBase LayerHats, Gloves & ScarvesHoodies, Jackets & SweatsRunning Shoes & SlidesShorts & BottomsSports Bras, Underwear & SocksTeam ReplicaTee Shirts & VestsRUGBY BOOTSBOOTS BY BRANDAll Rugby BootsadidasAsicsCanterburyGilbertMizunoNikeOptimumVIEW...Adults Rugby BootsKids Rugby BootsAll Sale Rugby BootsRS Top 10 BootsSOLE TYPE & POSITIONFirm Ground BootsSoft Ground BootsBacks BootsForwards bootsBOOT ACCESSORIESFootwear ExtrasInsolesWOMENS RUGBYTeam ReplicaView AllEngland InternationalScotland InternationalWales InternationalRugby BootsView AllBacks BootsForwards bootsBody ProtectionView AllHeadguardsShoulder PadsMouthguardsSports Bras, Underwear, SocksView AllSports BrasCompression SocksPlaying & Training SocksBase LayerView AllTop HalfBottom HalfHoodies, Jackets, TopsView AllHoodiesJacketsTopsT-Shirts, Vests, Tanks View AllT-ShirtsVests, TanksCompression TeesHats, Gloves, ScarvesView AllShorts & BottomsView AllShortsBaselayerBottoms & TrousersRunning shoes, SlidesView AllGym EquipmentView AllPROTECTION & EQUIPMENTPROTECTIVE WEARHeadguardsShoulder padsMouthguardsRUGBY BALLSMatch BallsTraining BallsTeam & Other BallsRugby World Cup BallsPumps & AdaptorsTRAINING EQUIPMENTGym & Home FitnessTackle Bags & TubesRucking ShieldsAgility TrainingBall Carry BagsTraining BibsRugby PostsPitch AccessoriesPLAYER ACCESSORIESDrinks BottlesKicking TeesHoldalls, Bags, BackpacksMittsGrip Sprays, WaxTrionZ Magnetic TherapyINJURY MANAGEMENTSupportsTaping, StrappingHot & Cold TherapyFirst Aid KidsRUGBY TEAMWEARADIDASShirtsShortsSocksCANTERBURYMensWomensKidsGILBERTMensWomensKidsUNBRANDED TEAMWEARMensWomensKidsGirlsWACKYSOXAdultsKidsBRANDSAdidasCanterburyGilbertMacronOptimumUmbroUnder ArmourSALEMENBootsTeam ReplicaTraining & Off-FieldProtection & EquipmentWOMENBootsTeam ReplicaTraining & Off-FieldProtection & EquipmentKIDSBootsTeam ReplicaTraining & Off-FieldProtection & EquipmentCOLLECTIONSView All Sale ProductsRugby World Cup 2019BootsProtection & EquipmentNew Zealand All BlacksEnglandScotland
Home>
Help Centre>
Privacy Policy
Help Centre Home
CHRISTMAS INFORMATIONHelp Centre HomeHow to ShopMaking a PaymentDelivery & ShipmentGuarantee, Returns & Faulty GoodsYour Customer AccountSize ChartPrivacy PolicyCookie PolicyGeneral Terms & ConditionsContact Us
Toggle Dropdown
Privacy Policy
CHRISTMAS INFORMATIONHelp Centre HomeHow to ShopMaking a PaymentDelivery & ShipmentGuarantee, Returns & Faulty GoodsYour Customer AccountSize ChartPrivacy PolicyCookie PolicyGeneral Terms & ConditionsContact Us
Privacy Policy
Privacy StatementUpdated Tuesday 25 August 2020.Rugbystore Ltd, t/a Rugbystore ("Rugbystore"), is committed to protecting the privacy and security of our customers and visitors and this notice explains the ways in which we collect and use data through our website and dealings with you. If you have any questions, please contact us on privacy@rugystore.co.uk.For all our services Rugbystore is the data controller – the company that is responsible for your privacy.What information do we collect & How do we use it and most importantly, why.We collect, and you provide us with various pieces of personal information, which we may use in several different ways. The following tables set out what we do and why we do it.Your name and contact detailsHow we use your name and contact detailsWhy do we use it?To process your orders and to deliver your purchasesThis information also forms part of our purchase contract with you. We must use this information to provide instruction to suppliers and to couriers on how to deliver your productsTo send you service messages by Email, Post, Text or through our website and applicationsWe do this to keep you up to date with the progress of your ordersTo send you information via email, SMS and postWe use this information to keep you up to date with relevant products, services, offers or notifications. We only do this with your permission which you can remove at any timeFor product and service reviewsTo get customer feedback on the products we sell and improve our customer service based on service feedback.For fraud prevention and detectionTo prevent and detect fraud against either yourselves or RugbystoreShowing you adverts as you browse the webSome products we offer can sell out very quickly. We do this so you can be aware of the latest products availableFinding out what you, and other customers, like and are interested inFrom time to time we may contact you to ensure we are giving you what you want and striving to do moreYour date of birth informationHow we use your date of birthWhy?Fraud preventionTo help protect your account and ourselves from fraudulent activityAge verificationWe make every effort to ensure that our customers are over 13 years of age. This is simply compliance to responsible retailing standardsYour genderHow we use your genderWhy?To improve your experienceWe use gender information to help provide more personalised experiences on the website or in our product recommendationsYour payment informationWe do not store Credit card information nor do we share customers details with any 3rd parties.How we use your payment informationWhy?Fraud preventionTo help protect your account and ourselves from fraudulent activityTake payment and give refundsWe need this to perform our contract with you and fulfil customer service duties to youEnsure communications are relevantWe have customers on different payment systems with us, we want to make sure that our messaging is aligned to this and relevant to each customerYour contact history with usInformation such as what you’ve said to us and how – i.e. over email you may have wanted to unsubscribe to a mailing list, or on social media or via the phone you may have wanted to look up an order status.How we use your contact historyWhy?Provide customer service and supportWe need to use information like this to provide basic customer services duties such as tracking down an orderTrain our staffWe may use interactions with members of staff as a training example to work towards providing better customer servicesTo inform marketing communicationsWe take feedback seriously, we do not want to irritate people and your feedback and data will assist our future planningPurchase historyWhat you've bought online.How we use your purchase historyWhy?Provide customer service and supportWe must do this to perform our contract with you and we make every effort to help provide customers with positiveProduct & Service reviewsWe may share your purchase information, name and email address with third party reviewing platforms, Feefo for example, for the purpose of gathering feedback on the product we sell and improving our customer service based on service reviews.Finding out what you, and other customers, likeTo try to give you what you want so you can make the most of your website experience. This information is also used to plan so our product range can be better aligned to your desiresTo provide you with recommendations of other things you might likeWe’ll help you navigate your way through our range of products by using the website to help point out products you might enjoyInformation about your device (phone, laptop, desktop or tablet) and how you use our website and applicationsInformation you give us as you browse the website, interact with it. This may include information such as current location if you choose to share it.How we use Information about your device (phone, laptop, desktop or tablet) and how you use our website and other applicationsWhy?Improve our website and set default experiences for you (such as language, age verification or login status)To obtain a better understanding of what and how our website is used, which we hope to use to create a better experience for you and our other customers.Protect our websiteTo prevent and detect against fraud to either you or Rugbystore. We will also need this to meet our legal obligations for looking after your dataInformation from accounts you link to usWhat we do if you linked your Amazon account or a social media account.How we use information from accounts you link to usWhy?To improve your experience of interacting with Rugbystore’s website – like checking out or making an account with usTo make your Rugbystore experience more enjoyable. To make your interactions with us easier.To provide you with product recommendationsMaking it easier for you to spot things which might be of interest to you.Your responses to surveys, competitions and promotionsHow we use your responses to surveys, competitions and promotionsWhy?To pick winners, take feedback onboard and improve our methods of interacting with membersWe use this information to improve the way we interact with our customers such as developing our service offering or tailoring our promotions to be more appealing.You don’t have to give us all this information, but some of it is necessary so that we can perform our contract obligations with you. You may not be able to buy from the website, or receive an optimal customer experience, if you withhold certain information or opt out of various communications types and methods. However, we will do our best to honour your decisions and will always work to uphold strict policies and processes to protect your data.We also take steps to anonymise and aggregate personal information (so that it does not identify you) and use it for the purposes including IT systems, research, data analysis, improving our website and other online properties, and developing new products and services. We may share this with third parties whose products are or may become available on our website or who provide us with support in conducting business and service improvements.Sharing your informationWe do not, and will not, sell any of your personal data to any third party – including your name, address, email address or payment information.However, we share your data with the following categories of companies as an essential part of being able to provide our services to you, as set out in this statement:Suppliers of products on the website where there is any need for ongoing services such as refunds, replacements or warranty issuesCompanies that work in support of Rugbystore, such as payment service providers, warehouses, order packers, and delivery companiesCompanies that provide product and service review aggregation, such as Feefo, so we can gather feedback on your shopping experience with rugbystoreProfessional service providers, such as marketing agencies, web development and optimisation partners, database administrators, advertising partners and website hosts, who help us run our business and need this information to help us do things betterGovernment entities, law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies, so we can help tackle fraud and comply with legislationCompanies approved by you, such as social media sites (if you choose to link your accounts to us) and payment providers who may link an account to your Rugbystore accountWe may also provide third parties with aggregated but anonymised information and analytics about our customers and, before we do so, we will make sure that it does not identify you.Marketing messagesIf you register an account with Rugbystore, we think knowing about the products we can offer is a fundamental benefit of your account. When you register, we will send you marketing messages unless you ask us not to, which you can do immediately or at any time.If you shop with us but do not wish to have an account, for example if you give us your details when you order a gift, as you will have purchased from us we presume you will be interested in being kept up to date with our offers and that we therefore have a legitimate interest to contact you. You will however be able to opt out of this at any time.We may send you marketing messages by email, post, text and push notification to keep you aware of the latest news from Rugbystore. You can choose whether or not to receive them in any of these ways by logging in and accessing the My Account settings on our website or by getting in touch with us.How to stop marketing messagesIf you don’t want to receive marketing messages from us, in a specific way or at all, the best way to do this is via the My Account Settings on our website, which will help you control all your notification settings.You can edit your marketing messaging settings by:Visiting the My Account SettingsClick the unsubscribe links in any emails or SMS messagingContacting the Rugbystore team on:
Email: sales@rugbystore.co.ukTelephone: 01721 726920 – Monday to Friday 08:30 am to 5:00 pm UK time excluding bank and public holidaysOnce you have done this we will make sure your profile is updated and you don’t receive unwanted marketing materials from us. Please note, due to our technical set up the impacts of any changes may take up to 48 hours to take effect – in the meantime we apologise for any inconvenience caused.Rugbystore advertising onlineRugbystore engage in online advertising to attract new customers, to keep you aware of what we are up to and to help you find and see our products.Like many other companies, we target banners and ads to you when you are on other websites, applications and search engines. This is done using a variety of digital marketing techniques including ad exchanges and marketing networks using several advertising technologies like web beacons, pixels, ad tags, cookies, mobile identifies, as well as specific services offered by some sites and social networks (such as Facebook’s Custom Audience services). We adhere to all advertiser policies and stick to strict rules and regulations set out by several advertising standards bodies as well as alcohol and spirits marketing policies.The banners and ads you will see are based on information we hold about you, or your previous use of our website. This includes information from the products you may have browsed on our website, the content you have engaged with or the advertising you may have previously responded to.Keeping your information, data sharing and transfersRetentionWe shall retain information as necessary to meet legal or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse or enforce our terms and conditions. We may also need to keep your details if you have asked us not to contact you with marketing, to ensure you do not accidentally hear from us again.TransferWe need to share your data with other companies who process it to provide services for Rugbystore. Some of our data processors will process data we provide to them outside of the EU. We will protect your privacy and your rights in the contracts we hold with our processors.Your Rights – access and correctionsYou have a lot of rights that relate to your personal information:The right to be informed about how your personal information is being used – as set out in this NoticeThe right to access the personal information we hold about youThe right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you – which will largely be editable via the My Account settingsThe right to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances (except for any legal circumstances where we must retain the information)The right to stop direct marketing messages, which you can do through your account, and to withdraw consent for other consent-based processing at any timeThe right to request that we transfer elements of your data either to you or another service providerThe right to complain to your data protection regulator. For the UK this is the Information Commissioner’s Office (opens in a new window)If you want to exercise these rights, have a complaint, or just have questions, please contact us.Changes to protecting privacyWe may make changes to this page from time to time to reflect how we are processing data. If we make significant changes we will make this clear via the website or other communication. In these circumstances we will need to use personal contact details to contact you.CookiesWe use different forms of cookies to improve your web experiences and to improve our understanding of marketing. Please see our cookie notice for more information: Rugbystore Cookie PolicyHow to contact us / how to be removedWe don’t want to send our customers any communications they don’t want to receive. We’d like to hear from you if you feel we could have provided a better service or have any specific questions or concerns; about this policy or other supporting documents, would like us to stop using your information or want to exercise your rights as set out in this document or have complaints.You can get in touch via our privacy@rugystore.co.uk email address which will put you straight in touch with the members of staff who manage data privacy and security. Alternatively, you can contact us on the usual customer services points of contact:Email: sales@rugbystore.co.ukTelephone: 01721 726920 – Monday to Friday 08:30am to 4:30pm UK time excluding bank and public holidaysIf you wish to write to us, please send a letter addressed to:Rugbystore
Unit 8 Cavalry Park
Peebles
EH45 9BU
Sign up to our newsletter
Sign up to our newsletter and be the first to find out about:
New products & the latest kit
Exclusive discounts & Giveaways
Special offers & exclusive products
Thank you for signing up to our newsletter.
CHRISTMAS INFOHelp CentreSize ChartDeliveryContactTrack your orderReturnsBlogGift Vouchers
© 2020 rugbystore.co.ukPrivacyTerms & ConditionsCookies
Shop with confidence
Christmas InformationGift VouchersContact usDelivery detailsTrack your orderReturnsOrder before 1pm for same day* despatch (*mon-fri).Free Standard UK delivery available on orders over £75.
Official suppliers of:
Canterbury of New ZealandadidasUnder ArmourMacronGilbertOptimum
Flexible Shipping Options:
Our shipping charges give you great rates no matter where you are in the world.Need it in a hurry? We've got next day services to get you the kit you need, when you need it.Click here to find out more about our UK, Europe and worldwide shipping charges.
Follow us...
Get involved in the rugbystore social network, special offers, up to date news, the latest products...
We accept:
rugbystore supportsThe White Ribbon Campaign
© 2020 rugbystore.co.ukContact UsSitemapTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyCookie PolicyPowered by Inforgen
